<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<DialogCollection>
	<Dialogs>
		<Dialog name = "Crew">
			<Texts>
				<Text face = "0">Captain...</Text>
				<Text face = "1">Captain....you...awake.....</Text>
				<Text face = "0">Hey....reaching....port....</Text>
				<Text face = "1">GET UP!!!</Text>
			</Texts>
		</Dialog>
		<Dialog name = "Secretary">
			<Texts>
				<Text face = "0">Geez...sleeping on the job...and this is your first day too...!</Text>
				<Text face = "0">We are just about to reach the Wingly's port. The crew has got me to check up on you...</Text>
				<Text face = "0">Sigh...I'm going to close one eye this time. but I need you to get up and direct the ship operations now. </Text>
				<Text face = "0">Come to the bridge when you're ready.</Text>
				<Text face = "0">...</Text>	
			</Texts>
		</Dialog>
		<Dialog name = "Secretary">
			<Texts>
				<Text face = "0">Well, captain. This is your first time with us. so I'm going to give you a quick brief on our ship's operations</Text>
				<Text face = "0">First of all, Take a look at the indicator on the top of the screen. This shows our estimated progress to reach our destination, Wingly's port.</Text>
				<Text face = "0">Our journey will be complete once the ship icon reaches the goal icon.</Text>
				<Text face = "0">Next, look at the ship information window. It contains several information, such as the ship's health, speed and the structural layout of our ship.</Text>	
						
			</Texts>
		</Dialog>
		<Dialog name = "Secretary">
			<Texts>
				<Text face = "1">Lets begin by learning how to direct orders to your crew</Text>
				<Text face = "2">First, select myself using the left mouse button</Text>
				<Text face = "2">Next, Use the left mouse button again to direct me to the specified location.</Text>
				<Text face = "2">Now, try to have to have me move to the zone indicated.</Text>
			</Texts>
		</Dialog>
		<Dialog name = "Secretary">
			<Texts>
				<Text face = "1">Excellent, now lets learn how to have your crew members work on </Text>
				<Text face = "2">First, select myself using the left mouse button</Text>
				<Text face = "2">Next, Use the left mouse button again to direct me to the specified location.</Text>
				<Text face = "2">Now, try to have to have me move to the zone indicated.</Text>
			</Texts>
		</Dialog>
	</Dialogs>	
</DialogCollection>

